

CONTACT

+355 69 274 7070

+39 351 5807264

EDUCATION

05.2021 - 06.2023 DOMINUSOFT

Software developer
Python | Django

SKILLS

- Html
- Css
- Bootstrap
- Javascript
- j-Query
- Sweetalerts
- Python
- Django
- · Django Rest Framework
- Celery
- · Celery Beat
- Redis
- Docker
- CI/CD Pipeline
- Mailgun

LANGUAGES

- Albanian (Mother language)
- English (B2)
- Italian (A2)

JONI ENESI

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

PROFILE

I first started to learn about creating websites in high school, but when I started to study it and put it into practice, it happened in 2021. I decided to create a simple website like "To Do List", a website for a law office to my friends, ect. Over the years, I deepened my knowledge about this profession by developing large websites, e-commerce in a more advanced way, minimizing many lines of code and using more the logic that programming languages possess; giving customers who have navigated my websites a nice experience and leaving them satisfied. Today as we speak, I have very good skills both side of web developing, in the frontend and in the backend, which is the part that I like to work the most.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Dominusoft

Python Web Developer

05.2021 - 06.2023

Full development and completion of the 3-years intensive course as well as the provision of certificates from the course. The work of the course project (e-commerce) correctly and within the requirements, completed before the delivery deadline entitled "Joni Rental Car" which deals with a rental car store, catalog, reservation and payment. At the end of the project, the presentation, the provision of certificates and the winning of the internship in the course.

Dominusoft

FULL STACK DEVELOPER INTERNSHIP

07.2023 - 08.2023

The development of the full internship as well as the provision of certificates from the Ministry of Economy and Finance. • The development of an E-commerce entitled "Internet from space". Project which is based on the sale-purchase of internet products. Integration of payment with Paypal as well as with card. • Delivery of the project on time, fully completed, presentation and provision of certificate.



CONTACT

+355 69 274 7070

+39 351 5807264

EDUCATION

05.2021 - 06.2023 DOMINUSOFT

Software developer
Python | Django

SKILLS

- Html
- Css
- Bootstrap
- Javascript
- j-Query
- Sweetalerts
- Python
- Django
- Django Rest Framework
- Celery
- · Celery Beat
- Redis
- Docker
- CI/CD Pipeline
- Mailgun

LANGUAGES

- Albanian (Mother language)
- English (B2)
- Italian (A2)

WORK EXPERIENCE

Dominusoft - FULL STACK DEVELOPMENT INTERNSHIP(Second)

08.2023 - 10.2023

BeHind

Development of an E-commerce related to trips from the BeHind agency to different countries. Expanded information for the customer on the Landing Page, the photo/video section to bring the customer closer to what awaits him during the journey. Searching for tickets, different flight schedules, reserving the ticket and paying by card or Paypal.

TRACKI LLC - Software Developer

10.2023 - Present

<u>eGift</u>

Development of an E-commerce related to Gift Cards of various companies such as Adidas, Nike Sephora, Apple Store, etc. A gift opportunity through a gift card tool from the client and sending it to the host person by email on a certain date and time with values according to the client. Card design in different ways in the form of thanksgiving or birthday etc. Payment by credit/debit card using POK Pay. It's the biggest project I've ever worked on just with the continuous tasks. A project which is detailed in the best way, starting from the designs, the logic and the way of ordering the products, their payment and the delivery of these gifts. Sending welcome emails of payment, invoice, gift. All together giving customers an extraordinary experience of making gifts to their loved ones.

<u>Scannlay Digital Menu</u>

06.2024 - Present

The opportunity and a great help for businesses such as coffee bars, lounges, restaurants. By scanning a QR code you can navigate on your phone the menu of the business you are visiting. Also the customer can send his order from his phone. And not only for customers but also for businesses a good opportunity to improve their service by having their own page for taking orders, daily summary, creating categories, specific menus for each business.